# Zahra Olanrewaju Junior Front End Developer

I am a vision driven graduate with experience working with Revit, AutoCad, Dynamo, Illustrator, Photoshop and Indesign. I am proactively client focused with emphasis on bringing creative concept into feasible and practical reality. Prioritizing and contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining customer and client satisfaction. I have very good communication, technical and team-working skills combined with a creative flair.

# **Education and Certification**

**2021-Present:** SheCodes Basic, Plus and Pro - Coding Course, Workshop and Challenges.

**2018-2020:** The University of Plymouth BA Architecture - 2:1

**2016-2017**: The University of Brighton BA Architecture

2013-2016: Archbishop Tenison's School 6th Form - 4 A levels - A - C

2008-2013: St Saviour's and StOlave's - 12 GCSE - A\* - C

# Internship

**2014 :** Trainee Assistant to Treasury Funding Investment Banker, Nationwide Headquarters, London.

- My internship at Nationwide Headquarters provided an insight into investment banking the various departments and challenges within investment banking. I gained organization, presentational and time management skills, emphasizing on deadlines and communication to ensure meetings are prepared in a timely and efficient manner.

**2013 :** Trainee Assistant to Architectural Engineer Barbara Weiss Architects, London.

- During my internship at Barbara Weiss Architects, I had the opportunity to learn and work in an effective and independent way, showcasing collaborative communication and negotiation skills. I had the opportunity to go on a site visit to Wokingham medical centre while under construction, gaining presentation and scheduling experience. While having the opportunity to sit in on meetings, understanding the research and context of a project. Highlighting the importance of collaboration within architectural and construction industry. The internship gave me an amazing opportunity to develop design and technical skills and understanding.

#### **2011**: Assistant to Architect Balfour Beatty Construction, London.

- Through my internship at Balfour Beatty Construction, I was a student liaison. Working between my secondary school student body and the architectural firm. This provided an insight into client architect relationship.

# Work Experience

2023- Present: English Tutor - IELTS (International English Language Testing)

**2021- Present :** Waitress/Runner - The Paxton

2018: Summer Sales Assitant - Gatwick Airport

2017: Christmas Sales Assitant - Card Factory

2017: Summer Office Staff/ Art Assistant - Camp America

2016: Christmas Sales Assitant - Liberty London - Department Store

2015: Social Media Marketing Assistant - Armageddon Academy Fitness

# Personal Infomation

Zahra Bolanle Olanrewaju

#### Phone Number

07940999703

#### Email

zahrabola@hotmail.com

#### Online Portfolio

https://www.zbolanrewaju.com/

## Software Skills

Revit

AutoCad

Dynamo

SketchUp

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Excel

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Bootstrap

Editor

Hosting

Api NodeJs

Material UI

Cypress

## Links

https://github.com/zahrabola

https://www.ignitefutures.co.uk/pro-

file/zahra-olanrewaju/

https://www.instagram.com/zah-

ra.o.designs/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zahra-olanrewaju-24913019a/